const ActivePassiveQuestions = [
    {
        question: "(Active) She reads books (passive)?",
        options: ["Books are read by her.", "Books read by her.", "Books is read by her", "Books were read by her."],
        correct_option: "Books are read by her"
    },
    {
        question: "Passive The cake was baked by Martha Active?",
        options: ["Martha baked the cake.", "Martha was baking the cake.", "Martha has baked the cake.", "Martha has baked the cake."],
        correct_option: "Martha baked the cake"
    },
    {
        question: "Active They will clean the room Passive?",
        options: ["The room is being cleaned by them.", "The room cleans by them.", "The room will be cleaned by them.", "The room cleaned by them."],
        correct_option: "The room will be cleaned by them"
    },
    {
        question: "Passive The letter was written by John Active?",
        options: ["John wrote the letter.", "John was writing the letter.", "John has written the letter.", "John is writing the letter."],
        correct_option: "John wrote the letter"
    },
    {
        question: "Active: The dog chased the cat Passive?",
        options: ["The cat was chased by the dog.", "The cat chased by the dog.", "The cat has been chased by the dog", "The cat is chased by the dog."],
        correct_option: "The cat was chased by the dog"
    },
    {
        question: "Passive: The movie was watched by millions. Active?",
        options: ["Millions watched the movie.", "Millions were watching the movie.", "Millions have watched the movie.", "Millions are watching the movie."],
        correct_option: "Millions watched the movie"
    },
    {
        question: "Active: He sings a song. Passive?",
        options: ["A song is sung by him.", "A song is sung by him", "A song was sung by him", "A song is singing by him"],
        correct_option: "A song is sung by him"
    },
    {
        question: "Passive: The house was built by the contractor. Active?",
        options: ["The contractor builds the house.", "The contractor built the house.", "The contractor was building the house.", "The contractor has built the house."],
        correct_option: "The contractor built the house"
    },
    {
        question: "Active: They are painting the fence. Passive?",
        options: ["The fence is being painted by them.", "The fence paints by them.", "The fence was painted by them.", "The fence is painted by them."],
        correct_option: "The fence is being painted by them"
    },
    {
        question: "Passive: The message was sent by Sarah. Active:?",
        options: ["Sarah sent the message.", "Sarah was sending the massage.", "Sarah sends the massage.", "Sarah has sent the massage."],
        correct_option: "Sarah sent the message"
    }
];

export default ActivePassiveQuestions;
